https://www.adart.com/privacy-policy

ADART.COM PRIVACY POLICY
Welcome to AdArt.Com (the “Site”).We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business.This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visitwithouttransacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by AdArt.com (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).“Personally Identifiable Information” refers to any information that identifies orcan be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, faxnumber, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not includeinformation that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification ofthe individual user)or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of theadvertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.What organizations are collecting the information?In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party servicevendors (such as credit card companies, clearing houses and banks) who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect thisinformation from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control howthese third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose howthey use personal information provided to them from Visitors and AuthorizedCustomers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely aslinks in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use theinformation given to them.How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?We use Personally Identifiable Information tocustomize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customersabout research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or informationrelated to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use PersonallyIdentifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers inresponse to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.With whom may the information may be shared?Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may be shared with other Authorized Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with otherAuthorized Customers. We may share aggregated information about our Visitors,including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with ouraffiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to”opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?Personally Identifiable Information collected by AdArt.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of AdArt.com except for use as indicated above.What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by respondingto emails as instructed, or by contacting us at CustomerService@AdArt.comAre Cookies Used on the Site?Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. Weuse Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and theservices they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on andthe site is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.How does AdArt.com use login information?AdArt.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.What partners or service providers haveaccess to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or AuthorizedCustomers on the Site?AdArt.com has entered into and willcontinue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number ofvendors.Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers forservice eligibility.Our privacy policy does not cover their collection oruse of this information.Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Informationto comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information inorder to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a lawenforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.How does the Site keep PersonallyIdentifiable Information secure?All of our employees are familiar withour security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information ofour Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number ofqualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to theinformation. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis.Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers,is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent overthe Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain asecure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors,tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such eventswill not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.How can Visitors correct anyinaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?Visitors andAuthorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at Supprt@AdArt.comCan a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally IdentifiableInformation collected by the Site?We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site’s database by contacting Support@AdArt.com.  However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible todelete a Visitor’s entry without retaining some residual information. Anindividual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivatedwill have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer,or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in anyway moving forward.What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know aboutchanges to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, ifwe are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer haspreviously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent suchdisclosure.Links:This web site contains links to otherweb sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are movingto another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
800-675-6353
info@adart.com
150 Executive Park Dr., Suite 2100, San Francisco, CA 94134
Facebook-f
Linkedin
Twitter
page links
Homepage
Sent out every so often, as not to overwhelm your email.
